<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[Fuu] Uncompromising Tribal Faction</name>
  <author>Fuu Chan</author>
  <packageId>Fuu.UncompromisingTribalFaction</packageId>
  <description>
The tribal faction is in a sorry state. In a world with either gun-toting, high tech, robotic, armored, or giant insect factions, it's a wonder the tribal faction has managed to survive at all.

After losing battle after battle, the chiefs got together to formulate a new battle strategy.

Tribal War Plan:
1. Gives tribal Breachers and Berserkers a 50% chance to spawn with volcanic ash filled "Smoke bombs", to cover their advance amidst gunfire.
2. Adds the tribal Fire thrower, a grenadier unit equipped with "Fire bombs" from "Vanilla Weapons Expanded - Tribal" to flush out defenders from their positions.
3. Gives tribal Breachers, Berserkers, and Chiefs "Battle banners" from "Vanilla Apparel Expanded - Accessories", to increase their pain threshold.
4. Gives all tribal Archers "Quivers" from "Vanilla Apparel Expanded - Accessories", to increase their ranged rate of fire.
5. Gives tribal Breachers, Archers, and Warriors normal quality gear instead of poor quality.
6. Tweaked raid unit spawn ratios for more effective battle groups.

New Item: Smoke Bomb 
  A small clay pot filled with fine volcanic ash. When smashed mid-air, it will release a small cloud of smoke, obscuring incoming shots and preventing turrets from locking on.
  Cost: 20 Stone bricks
  Cannot be refilled (2 charges)
  Smaller radius than smokepop belts

The goal of this mod was to make the tribals a proper and decent enemy faction, having their own strengths and requiring some strategy to take down, but not overpowered. Hope you enjoy!

*Optimized for performance.
*Safe to add mid-game.
*Not recommended to remove mid-game.
*Rocketman compatible.
*Rimthreaded compatible.
*CE compatible, but this was balanced around vanilla.
*Should be no conflicts unless you have a mod that makes unsafe modifications to the vanilla tribal faction.

Credits to: Oskar Potocki for the VE series and smoke bomb art.
Credits to: hamu koutarou for the artwork used in the thumbnail and tanosii_chan for the upvote animation! Give them a visit!
  </description>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>VanillaExpanded.VWETB</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Weapons Expanded - Tribal</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2454918552</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>VanillaExpanded.VAEAccessories</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Apparel Expanded — Accessories</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2521176396</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
    <li>VanillaExpanded.VWETB</li>
    <li>VanillaExpanded.VAEAccessories</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>